[
    {
      "question": "The Earth is approximately how many miles away from the Sun?",
      "answer1": "93 million",
      "answer2": "930 million",
      "answer3": "9.3 million",
      "answer4": "193 million",
      "correctAnswer": "93 million"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following landlocked countries is entirely contained within another country?",
      "answer1": " Luxembourg",
      "answer2": "Burkina Faso",
      "answer3": "Lesotho",
      "answer4": "Mongolia",
      "correctAnswer": "Lesotho"
    },
    {
      "question": "In a popular video game, Ms. Pac-Man gobbles up pellets while pursued by four ghosts named Inky, Binky, Pinky, and what?",
      "answer1": "Sue",
      "answer2": "Jane",
      "answer3": "Meg",
      "answer4": "Anne",
      "correctAnswer": "Sue"
    },
    {
      "question": "While visiting a museum in 2013, Justin Bieber caused a controversy when he stated he hoped who would have been a \"belieber?\"",
      "answer1": "Anne Frank",
      "answer2": "Eva Brown",
      "answer3": "Eleanor Roosevelt",
      "answer4": "Rita Hayworth",
      "correctAnswer": "Anne Frank"
    },
    {
      "question": "At the closest point, which island group is only 50 miles south-east of the coast of Florida?",
      "answer1": "Turks and Caicos Islands",
      "answer2": "US Virgin Islands",
      "answer3": "Bermuda",
      "answer4": "Bahamas",
      "correctAnswer": "Bahamas"
    },
    {
      "question": "Obstetrics is a branch of medicine particularly concerned with what?",
      "answer1": "Heart conditions",
      "answer2": "Broken bones",
      "answer3": "Childbirth",
      "answer4": "Old age",
      "correctAnswer": "Childbirth"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why are the colors of the Olympic Rings yellow, green, red, black, and blue?",
      "answer1": "Colours representing all humans",
      "answer2": "Colours of the founding countries of the Olympic Committee",
      "answer3": "Colours representing natural artifacts",
      "answer4": "Colours of every flag in the world",
      "correctAnswer": "Colours of every flag in the world"
    },
    {
      "question": "What year did Cambodia gain its independence from France?",
      "answer1": "1953",
      "answer2": "1958",
      "answer3": "1964",
      "answer4": "1949",
      "correctAnswer": "1953"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first lawyer to become US President?",
      "answer1": "John F. Kennedy",
      "answer2": "Bill Clinton",
      "answer3": "Aaron Burr",
      "answer4": "John Adams",
      "correctAnswer": "John Adams"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the 1988 movie \"Die Hard\", what does John McClane leave in the limo?",
      "answer1": "An umbrella",
      "answer2": "His suitcase",
      "answer3": "A gun",
      "answer4": "A teddy bear",
      "correctAnswer": "A teddy bear"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the school in the 1989 movie \"Dead Poets Society\"?",
      "answer1": "Hillman Academy",
      "answer2": "The Welton Academy",
      "answer3": "Harrison University",
      "answer4": "Rushmore Academy",
      "correctAnswer": "The Welton Academy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a group of locusts called?",
      "answer1": "Field",
      "answer2": "Plague",
      "answer3": "Archipelago",
      "answer4": "Conifers",
      "correctAnswer": "Plague"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the name of the first hominid chimp in space?",
      "answer1": "Rock",
      "answer2": "Bob",
      "answer3": "Ham",
      "answer4": "Kip",
      "correctAnswer": "Ham"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was murdered along with OJ Simpson’s estranged wife Nicole?",
      "answer1": "Chris Darden",
      "answer2": "Marcia Clarke",
      "answer3": "Alan Dershowitz",
      "answer4": "Ronald Goldman",
      "correctAnswer": "Ronald Goldman"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first person to swim across Lake Ontario?",
      "answer1": "Marilyn Bell",
      "answer2": "Dawn Fraser",
      "answer3": "Kristin Otto",
      "answer4": "Mark Spitz",
      "correctAnswer": "Marilyn Bell"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who invented the lint roller?",
      "answer1": "Nicholas McKay",
      "answer2": "Patricia Bath",
      "answer3": "Ralph H. Baer",
      "answer4": "Lonnie Johnson",
      "correctAnswer": "Nicholas McKay"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose final opera was called \"Death in Venice\"?",
      "answer1": "Benjamin Britten",
      "answer2": "Giuseppe Verdi",
      "answer3": "Giacomo Puccini",
      "answer4": "Leonard Bernstein",
      "correctAnswer": "Benjamin Britten"
    },
    {
      "question": "What color is the car that Starsky drives in the TV show \"Starsky & Hutch\"?",
      "answer1": "Red",
      "answer2": "Black",
      "answer3": "Blue",
      "answer4": "Green",
      "correctAnswer": "Red"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the comic book series \"Strangers in Paradise\", what item of clothing does Francine struggle to keep on during a high school play?",
      "answer1": "Her toga",
      "answer2": "Her wig",
      "answer3": "Her heels",
      "answer4": "Her glasses",
      "correctAnswer": "Her toga"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which German city was the birthplace of the poet Heinrich Heine?",
      "answer1": "Düsseldorf",
      "answer2": "Munich",
      "answer3": "Hamburg",
      "answer4": "Frankfurt",
      "correctAnswer": "Düsseldorf"
    },
    {
      "question": "Erik Rotheim patented the first aerosol spray can in Oslo in what year?",
      "answer1": "1927",
      "answer2": "1946",
      "answer3": "1903",
      "answer4": "1955",
      "correctAnswer": "1927"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which villain spoke the line \"Make like a tree, and get out of here\"?",
      "answer1": "Biff Tannen",
      "answer2": "Johnny Lawrence",
      "answer3": "Ace Merrill",
      "answer4": "Ed Rooney",
      "correctAnswer": "Biff Tannen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What former musician played bass on Madonna's \"Like a Prayer\"?",
      "answer1": "Randy Jackson",
      "answer2": "Geddy Lee",
      "answer3": "Flea",
      "answer4": "Jack Bruce",
      "correctAnswer": "Randy Jackson"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is the world’s largest parking lot?",
      "answer1": "Edmonton, Canada",
      "answer2": "Seattle, US",
      "answer3": "Toronto, Canada",
      "answer4": "Detroit, US",
      "correctAnswer": "Edmonton, Canada"
    },
    {
      "question": "What famous World War II general went into battle wearing two ivory-handled revolvers on his hips?",
      "answer1": "General George Patton",
      "answer2": "General Heinz Guderian",
      "answer3": "General Georgy Zhukov",
      "answer4": "General Douglas MacArthur",
      "correctAnswer": "General George Patton"
    },
    {
      "question": "In 1964, who became the first running back in NFL history to rush for more than 10,000 career yards?",
      "answer1": "Jim Brown",
      "answer2": "John Mackey",
      "answer3": "Jim Ringo",
      "answer4": "Gale Sayers",
      "correctAnswer": "Jim Brown"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose \"Small House\" is the subject of the play acted out during \"The King and I\"?",
      "answer1": "Uncle Thomas'",
      "answer2": "Uncle Carl's",
      "answer3": "Uncle Bill's",
      "answer4": "Uncle Peter's",
      "correctAnswer": "Uncle Thomas'"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who served as the United States Ambassador to Japan from 2013-2017?",
      "answer1": "Caroline Bouvier Kennedy",
      "answer2": "John Roos",
      "answer3": "Bill Hagerty",
      "answer4": "Howard Baker",
      "correctAnswer": "Caroline Bouvier Kennedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What actor was the executive producer of the mystery series \"Push, Nevada\"?",
      "answer1": "Ben Affleck",
      "answer2": "George Clooney",
      "answer3": "Brad Pitt",
      "answer4": "Chris Pine",
      "correctAnswer": "Ben Affleck"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said: \"Santa has the right idea. Visit people once a year.\"?",
      "answer1": "Victor Borge",
      "answer2": "Bill Burr",
      "answer3": "Lenny Bruce",
      "answer4": "Jerry Seinfeld",
      "correctAnswer": "Victor Borge"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is the Swimming Hall of Fame located?",
      "answer1": "Fort Lauderdale, Florida",
      "answer2": "New Orleans, Louisiana",
      "answer3": "Austin, Texas",
      "answer4": "San Diego, California",
      "correctAnswer": "Fort Lauderdale, Florida"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of wine accompanies Hannibal Lecter's liver and fava bean dinner?",
      "answer1": "Chianti",
      "answer2": "Pinot Noir",
      "answer3": "Syrah",
      "answer4": "Zinfandel",
      "correctAnswer": "Chianti"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which French fashion designer created the conical bra for Madonna's \"Blond Ambition\" tour?",
      "answer1": "Jean-Paul Gaultier",
      "answer2": "Thierry Mugler",
      "answer3": "Pierre Cardin",
      "answer4": "Yves Saint Laurent",
      "correctAnswer": "Jean-Paul Gaultier"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Dude from \"The Big Lebowski\" liked to drink what?",
      "answer1": "White Russians",
      "answer2": "Cosmopolitans",
      "answer3": "Long Island Iceteas",
      "answer4": "Espresso Martinis",
      "correctAnswer": "White Russians"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which two armies fought in the Battle of Blood River?",
      "answer1": "Boers & Zulus",
      "answer2": "Hutus & Tutsis",
      "answer3": "Hupas & Monos",
      "answer4": "Cados & Diggers",
      "correctAnswer": "Boers & Zulus"
    },
    {
      "question": "The world's longest tunnel, that is also used to supply water to New York City, is called what?",
      "answer1": "The Delaware Aqueduct",
      "answer2": "St. Gotthard",
      "answer3": "Mount Ovit",
      "answer4": "Micangshan",
      "correctAnswer": "The Delaware Aqueduct"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the fear of washing or bathing called?",
      "answer1": "Ablutophobia",
      "answer2": "Alektorophobia",
      "answer3": "Atelophobia",
      "answer4": "Anthophobia",
      "correctAnswer": "Ablutophobia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What scientist proposed the theory of continental drift?",
      "answer1": "Alfred Wegener",
      "answer2": "John Williams",
      "answer3": "Masaru Emoto",
      "answer4": "Joan Rose",
      "correctAnswer": "Alfred Wegener"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first female American in space?",
      "answer1": "Sally Ride",
      "answer2": "Mae Jemison",
      "answer3": "Krista Jennings",
      "answer4": "Nicole Mann",
      "correctAnswer": "Sally Ride"
    },
    {
      "question": "What US city is home to Pike Place Market?",
      "answer1": "Seattle",
      "answer2": "Chicago",
      "answer3": "Austin",
      "answer4": "Oklahoma City",
      "correctAnswer": "Seattle"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who follows Godel and Escher in the title of a 1979 book by Douglas Hofstadter?",
      "answer1": "Bach",
      "answer2": "Chopin",
      "answer3": "Mozart",
      "answer4": "Beethoven",
      "correctAnswer": "Bach"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose famous horse was named Buttermilk?",
      "answer1": "Dale Evans",
      "answer2": "Roy Rogers",
      "answer3": "Robin Rogers",
      "answer4": "Pat Brady's",
      "correctAnswer": "Roy Rogers"
    },
    {
      "question": "Selenophobia is the fear of what?",
      "answer1": "The Moon",
      "answer2": "The ocean",
      "answer3": "Mermaids",
      "answer4": "Chemicals",
      "correctAnswer": "The Moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Upon his death, what convicted killer donated his corneas?",
      "answer1": "Gary Gilmore",
      "answer2": "Ronnie Lee Gardner",
      "answer3": "John Spenkelink",
      "answer4": "John Albert Taylor",
      "correctAnswer": "Gary Gilmore"
    },
    {
      "question": "What common household object appears in the opening scene of the film \"The Sixth Sense\"?",
      "answer1": "A light bulb",
      "answer2": "A door knob",
      "answer3": "A curtain",
      "answer4": "A fork",
      "correctAnswer": "A light bulb"
    },
    {
      "question": "What position was first held by Steve Allen?",
      "answer1": "Tonight Show host",
      "answer2": "First secretary general of US",
      "answer3": "The creative director of Vogue",
      "answer4": "CEO of Google",
      "correctAnswer": "Tonight Show host"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which country was Greta Garbo born?",
      "answer1": "Sweden",
      "answer2": "Germany",
      "answer3": "Bulgaria",
      "answer4": "France",
      "correctAnswer": "Sweden"
    },
    {
      "question": "The journey in Roald Dahl's \"James and the Giant Peach\" ends with the peach impaled on what?",
      "answer1": "The Empire State Building",
      "answer2": "A grocery store",
      "answer3": "The Hollywood sign",
      "answer4": "A grandma's house",
      "correctAnswer": "The Empire State Building"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did Robert Frost sum up everything he learned about life?",
      "answer1": "'It goes on'",
      "answer2": "'Money can't buy life'",
      "answer3": "'I'm bored with it all'",
      "answer4": "'I want nothing but death'",
      "correctAnswer": "'It goes on'"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which literary work's title character is named Prince Myshkin?",
      "answer1": "The Idiot",
      "answer2": "A Clockwork Orange",
      "answer3": "Crime and Punishment",
      "answer4": "The Trial",
      "correctAnswer": "The Idiot"
    }
]

